DIMA SABILA

dimashabella05@gmail.com

+62 882-9950-7420

www.linkedin.com/in/dima-sabila

Profile Summary

6th semester Informatics Engineering student who wants to develop a career and professionalism in the field of technology. During college, I had organizational experience in running several work programs and was active in the management as a secretary. have a great interest in design and like to edit videos and images. have effective communication skills, adaptable, can work together in teams, and understand quickly. I hope to gain new experiences and use the skills I have to develop and succeed in the world of work.

Education

• SMA Negri 1 Meulaboh

2017 - 2020

Natural Science

Gunadarma University - Depok

2021 - Present

6th Semester Informatics Engineering Student Total GPA: 3.78 / 4.00

Experience

Studi Independen - PT Mitra Talenta Grup Web Development & UI/UX Design

Februari, 2024 - Juni, 2024

• Micro Project | Designer

Responsible for Research and create Hi-Fi User Interfaces for website design. such as Mock-Up, Wireframe, User Flow and Prototype.

• Massive Project | Project Manager

Responsible for planning, executing, and designing to make the project successful. create a website by going through the stages of research, interviews with stakeholders, journaling, and execution.

Marketing - PT Bossco Sentral Perkasa

2020 - 2021

Offers import handling services online via phone or email, for costume processing at Tanjung Priuk Port and Soekarna Hatta Airport.

Organization

Himpunan Masyarakat Teknik Informatika

2021 - Present

Arts & Creative Media Division | Secretary

Responsible for records, money and making proposal letters, as well as supervising and coordinating division activities. Active in participating in division work programs.

Volunteer Group Supervisor at PKKMB FTI

September, 2022

As a group advisor (pk), the purpose is to help and guide new students to get information about the campus.

• Volunteer Decoration and Documentation Team at Basketin

July, 2022

Being part of the decoration and documentation division which designs posters and documents during the event.

competency

- · Programming Languages: Python, Java, Golang dan HTML
- Design Tools: Canva, Figma dan Draw.io
- Microsoft Office: Word, Excel, and Powerpoint
- · Proficient in teamwork, Adaptability, Creative Thinking, Analytical Thinking, and Problem Solving
- Language and Communication: Bahasa Indonesia (Native), Bahasa Inggris (Beginner)